<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<contentList date="26/10/2020 01:10">
  <content contentuid="he31a9393g336cg4b49gae37g887f69aefc33" version="1">Shadow's Heart</content>
  <content contentuid="h1037f1fbgd8fdg47a3ga9f5g602f8e783551" version="1">Once a relic of shadow, now reborn in dawnfire. This mace channels the light of Lathander through hands once touched by darkness, uniting redemption and radiance.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc1df4ef1g6d29g4341g91f2gd91b4645fbe8" version="1">Argentum</content>
  <content contentuid="hc1aa21b3g0aa5g4fadg9425g43c433be36c6" version="1">Forged in the first light of dawn, Argentum shines with the brilliance of Lathander’s grace. Each strike burns away shadow, blinding the wicked and purging the undead.</content>
  <content contentuid="h9ac3b253g6c43g4600g9b26ga8f92332ab84" version="1">Tonitrum</content>
  <content contentuid="h1f76d3d5gc1a1g467dg92ceg507f9ca5270a" version="1">Forged in the first light of dawn and quenched in stormcloud tears, Tonitrum sings with the thunderous joy of Lathander’s creation. Each strike carries the light of renewal and the fury of the storm — cleansing the world in radiance and sound.</content>
  <content contentuid="h7eb5f572g06e4g4a77g9b88g0a91a5aa9679" version="1">Patentibus</content>
  <content contentuid="h8aff4f28g0807g47bcg88fcg75f55b394aba" version="1">A Staff of Opening</content>
  <content contentuid="h1e7141c6g2cf5g49c6ga390gdd1d6721383d" version="1">Tonitrolus</content>
  <content contentuid="h2f4f6be4g8bb1g4416gb5b2g9fb223c06d83" version="1">An Axe of Thunder</content>
  <content contentuid="h41e411aeg36a8g43b1gb751ge5288d851e66" version="1">Malevolence</content>
  <content contentuid="hf4a8a6bdgb761g45e8g823cg7fee7be50e92" version="1">A bitter dagger</content>
  <content contentuid="haef54d3dg4602g436fg87f4gfb14543bfe78" version="1">Malice</content>
  <content contentuid="h14a39b16g2226g4fc3gb895g1e3e25444a50" version="1">Another bitter dagger</content>
  <content contentuid="hc5876b7fg8db7g4e9ag8e89g7c56f343d1a6" version="1">Jubar</content>
  <content contentuid="h556a1a5cg7893g4d2bga89ag798e466340c7" version="1">A scimitar channeling the Morninglord's light to enhance the druid's powers</content>
  <content contentuid="h74f6f1e6g6a8cg4e82g88a5g914ea22b4950" version="1">Moonshadow</content>
  <content contentuid="h7e2ad7e8g185fg4f6egb2beg9a2de1560e74" version="1"> A nimble scimitar that glimmers with moonlight, granting swiftness and the power to blind foes with its radiant strikes</content>
  <content contentuid="h3b21f8e6ge85dg4d4cgafedgcf649d000c54" version="1">Warpbinder Amulet</content>
  <content contentuid="hd8088b1fg63d7g4e8fg9ebfg17636f7943f2" version="1">An enchanted amulet that allows its wearer to traverse vast distances in the blink of an eye.</content>
  <content contentuid="727369c2-ea46-4f8d-81e9-742fc4c6602b" version="1">Gravebinder's Mantle</content>
  <content contentuid="4eb38fc0-a906-4cf2-bcb9-f03f801df7f9" version="1">This robe emanates a chilling aura, woven with threads of shadow and whispers from beyond the grave. Only those attuned to the necrotic arts dare to don its power.</content>
  <content contentuid="h4ef4fbe7g9c4ag46d6g9e75g8d3c17e52d56" version="1">Moonfinger</content>
  <content contentuid="h8f3bdc81g46ddg4b05g87b0g21a2e61db0ec" version="1">It glints only under starlight and never casts a shadow</content>
  <content contentuid="hbbc372f8g9756g4f18g941fg5e9214f947a7" version="1">Fly (Moonfinger)</content>
  <content contentuid="hf1185af6g082bg4fb4gae16g263ce5435b03" version="1">Take flight up to <LSTag Tooltip="Distance">30m</LSTag>, borne on moonlight and wind.</content>
  <content contentuid="he0f8a879g9ed0g4765gad81g144a58a1dd3b" version="1">Moon Bomb</content>
  <content contentuid="h77d81a59g5579g45f1gbb76g0b4ae5754049" version="1">Hurl a condensed sphere of moonlight that bursts in a dazzling flash on impact, searing foes with 3d6 Radiant damage. Agile targets may dodge the worst of it, taking only half damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="hb901158eg8f15g458ag9b7dg10fc28b8fa53" version="1">Second Dawn</content>
  <content contentuid="h329f6553g4823g4bd4gbd2eg41483e44e4a2" version="1">From the radiant heart of the Morninglord comes a light no shadow can endure. In the hush before the sun’s rise, you call forth Lathander’s gift of renewal, and all things begin anew.</content>
  <content contentuid="hd17791c2g9ffag4387gbdc8ga668b997adb5" version="1">Furybound</content>
  <content contentuid="h4dd4d754g0ee6g492agab96g8fe8acb97df4" version="1">Forged from hides scarred by battle and storms alike, these garments hum with untamed fury. To wear them is to stride as the wild itself.</content>
  <content contentuid="hfd5ad259g5b1fg4da2gaa93g6959e41c3f3b" version="1">Lockbane</content>
  <content contentuid="h6baf6ff9ge234g4e32ga1e2g1bbaeebcc6fa" version="1">This ring bends wards and seals to the wearer’s will, opening what is shut and securing what lies unbound.</content>
  <content contentuid="h8c90410egbc07g47b8g8d2aga4a7c84ca5d9" version="1">Dawnstrider</content>
  <content contentuid="ha58463ebg0304g455dg892fg2f2ec4c4aee1" version="1">Sung into being by the high priestesses of Corellon during the First Dawn, this bow was gifted to a mortal champion who could stride as fast as the light itself. Its string hums with celestial swiftness, and each arrow loosed leaves a trail of radiant fire that guides allies to their mark.</content>
  <content contentuid="haa5f950eg4e66g4b24g95fdgaab3b568668a" version="1">When struck by thunderous force, reverberations build within the target. The effect explodes in a clap of sound, dealing minor Thunder damage and potentially knocking the creature Prone if it fails a Constitution saving throw.</content>
  <content contentuid="h1aa5309dg9384g44c6gb856g48cd56546240" version="1">The Morninglord’s Mantle</content>
  <content contentuid="h4e405433g44c4g4184g8701gef0837c70947" version="1">A relic said to have belonged to St. Sollars the Twice-Martyred, who carried Lathander’s light into lands steeped in shadow.</content>
  <content contentuid="hf7ab1010g2e13g40eegaba0g8c4d05670bd4" version="1">Dawnforged Light</content>
  <content contentuid="h8f7cf2a5g8a86g45bega2e3g8b8984513df0" version="1">Radiates a brilliant aura of light within a <LSTag Tooltip="Distance">9m</LSTag> radius, granting immunity to all types of blindness to the party and blinding fiends and the undead.</content>
  <content contentuid="hc9a5f370g48f4g4706g954ag4df8260d52ad" version="1">Lathander's Sight</content>
  <content contentuid="h7b8239e9gcaa4g48f2gab1agd90140b3f920" version="1">Bathed in the Morninglord’s light, this creature cannot be blinded.</content>
  <content contentuid="hfbd269a3g8558g4d7cga786g045f7bb532bb" version="1">Dawnburst of Lathander</content>
  <content contentuid="h0e972ce5g43a0g4169g9c47ge6d482aceeaf" version="1">A radiant wave of dawnlight bursts from you, scorching the wicked and uplifting the faithful.</content>
  <content contentuid="h18be0eb8g4d5fg4990gbc20gbe1623f0d3b8" version="1">Ring of the Silver Threshold</content>
  <content contentuid="he37a0923g266fg445bg9fcfgb9126a752031" version="1">Forged in the liminal spaces between the Astral Plane and the waking mind, this ring hums faintly with psychic resonance. Githyanki warriors once wore such relics when storming the dream-realms of their enemies, the silver bands amplifying both thought and sinew in equal measure.</content>
  <content contentuid="hbceb0b7cgfd44g4aa5gadd1g34d41d8870b6" version="1">Silver Threshold</content>
  <content contentuid="h7f626137geb7bg4d4agbbdag071225681ec6" version="1">Your mind opens to the Astral flow, channeling pure thought into every strike. While under this effect, your weapon attacks deal an additional <LSTag Type="Damage" Tooltip="Psychic">1d8 Psychic</LSTag> damage.</content>
  <content contentuid="h25551b1ag8eceg44c4g8408g74c7e9d025a0" version="1">Dawnforged Hammer</content>
  <content contentuid="hb2785dc5g0276g4cbaga101g597d8af42f7d" version="1">Once a tool of tyranny in the deep forges of Gracklstugh, this hammer was purified in the dawn’s first light. Its Duergar wielder, once enslaved by darkness, now channels Lathander’s radiance through steel. Each strike carries the warmth of rebirth — even in the deepest shadows.</content>
  <content contentuid="hedaddb93gd9ecg48f8gb827gb81fe71360ae" version="1">Dawnstrike</content>
  <content contentuid="h88c4e86fg6e23g4232gbb13g5cd3681708da" version="1">You channel the breaking light of Lathander through your weapon, turning a single blow into a burst of holy brilliance. The strike carries both steel and sunrise—its impact sears the wicked and blinds those who dwell in shadow.</content>
  <content contentuid="h3fa10727g7f47g49d4g9ed9g7f88039f5006" version="1">Sunpiercer</content>
  <content contentuid="hb70c9a67g6e12g427cg82d9g58254c026506" version="1">Forged in the dim forges of the Deep and sanctified beneath the morning sun, Sunpiercer carries the faith of one who turned his back on shadow. Each bolt it fires burns with the first light of day — a judgment upon the darkness that once claimed its wielder.</content>
  <content contentuid="hee6fde79g43bbg4816gab53g6e775076911a" version="1">Touch of the Morninglord</content>
  <content contentuid="h46a451b5g02c4g4cd5g8839g88020c6d036c" version="1">Channel the Morninglord’s blazing light into your foe, burning away corruption and shadow with searing radiant power.</content>
  <content contentuid="h90402470gf5b4g418ag938cg98dcd928e762" version="1">Dawn Crusher</content>
  <content contentuid="hf2ac5c0dga0f5g4784ga703g7fe217c9af5c" version="1">Channel the Morninglord’s radiant fury into a single, devastating strike. Blinding light erupts on impact, crushing shadow and corruption beneath the dawn’s first fire.</content>
  <content contentuid="h26733642g5ff2g4192ga10cg0f8c6986eff5" version="1">Sunstring</content>
  <content contentuid="h7931d959g3bfeg4cb0ga53age615ca666396" version="1">This shortbow hums with the quiet promise of morning. When its string is drawn, a faint glow gathers along the limbs, as though the first light of dawn waits to be loosed upon the world.</content>
  <content contentuid="h867b5893g63dbg4cf7g87e1g222e2939cb41" version="1">Aegis</content>
  <content contentuid="h7ffb9502g2684g46e9g87d6g71381da507c6" version="1">Hammered from radiant-forged steel at the break of day, this plate bears the warmth of a rising sun. Its surface gleams with a soft golden sheen, and those who don it feel as though they stand at the threshold between night and morning, unyielding and resolute.</content>
</contentList>
